♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D. ♪
♪ There was a
guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jumpsuit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses
didn't like him so ♪
♪ They shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can
find, la-la-la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor
his mind, la-la-la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end, la-la-la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call,
Cambot, pan left ♪
♪ Gypsy, hi, girl ♪
♪ Tom Servo,
what a cool guy ♪
♪ Crow, he's a wisecracker ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science
facts, la la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really
just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000 ♪
(doors closing)
- See, this is a
Dutch navy rub,
the kind that give
you in the service.
Is that good, okay.
- Ow.
- Oh geez, hi.
Boy, it's really a hairy day.
I got a load of laundry
and I just got done
giving the robots a
bath, and I'm about to
put them down.
- No.
- Then, I got to clean
up the load pan bay.
- Uh, Servo messed it up.
- No, no it was both of us.
We were having sword
fights (chuckles).
- [Computer] 30 seconds
to commercial sign.
- Oh, stop it.
(all chattering)
- You guys just got to--
- Joel, tell him to stop.
- Would you take it easy?
You're just overtired.
- [Computer] Commercial
sign in, in 10 seconds.
- I don't want to
hear another peep
out of you two, all right?
- [Computer] Commercial
sign in, in five,
four, three, two, one.
- Eeee!
- All right, that's
it, that's it.
- Good one, Crow, come on.
- Nice one.
(upbeat instrumental music)
- I know you are
but what am I?
- Oh, you're another one.
- I know you are
but what am I?
- You're dumb.
- Baby, baby.
- Listen, you guys better
stop it or I'm going to
give you both a
time out, okay?
How's that make you feel?
- But, Joel,
Joel, you said we could
stay up for the movie.
- Yeah, that's what
we're designed for.
- Yeah.
- Listen, okay, if you're
really, really good,
you can stay up for
the movie, okay?
- Okay, we'll be really good.
- Yeah, we promise.
- Okay, now look sharp,
the mad scientists
are calling, all right?
- Hm, mm-hmm, okay.
Now, do you have that
prism lens effect?
That fly eye thing
we talked about?
You know like at the
beginning of Family Affair.
That kind of thing.
We'll do that
here, all right?
Well, Joel, we're just
tidying up down here a bit.
Let's get right to the
invention exchange this week.
What do you say,
how about it?
♪ We're going to
watch the movie ♪
♪ We get to watch the movie ♪
- Hey, come on, cut
it out you guys.
I want you to go turn out
the lights you spinach chins.
I want to show him
Gretchen the Slinky, okay?
That's better.
Well, some exciting
things have been going on
here in the
Satellite of Love.
I realize that if you gave
the right chemical bath
to a slinky and then
exposed it to some
ultraviolet light, some
interesting things would
happen.
I want to show you
Gretchen the Slinky.
Hey, Gretchen,
wake up, come on.
There you go.
See, she's doing really good.
Yeah, that's right, she
likes to be around people.
Come on, hey come on.
You want something to eat?
Here, I got some
carpet for you.
You like carpet, don't,
you don't like?
Oh, come on,
have some carpet.
Yeah, that's good.
Yeah, she loves carpet.
You want some more?
Come on, have some more
there, finish it up.
Okay, now let's
show them what
Slinkies do when
they sleep, okay?
I'm going to show them
how you sleep, okay?
Just hang you up like this.
See, they rock themselves
like that, okay.
All right, and do one last
thing for them Gretchen,
okay?
All right, I want you
to do one last thing.
I want you to do your
impression of the '60s, okay?
On the count of
three, all right?
One, two, three, do your
impression of the '60s.
That's good, all right, cool.
- That is adorable.
I wish I had one of those.
Must be kind of hard
to take care of, I bet.
I remember when
was a kid once,
I had this Slinky, I put
it on the escalator--
- [Dr. Forester] Frank!
- Oh, here comes Dr. Forester
now with his invention.
- Well, Joel, this
invention is based on the
old Slinky train
toy I had as a kid.
It allows me to be
in two places at once
connected by the
special bio tube.
Well, it's much
too complicated,
would take a scientist
to explain it,
and I'm simply too mad.
Well, what do
you think, Joel?
- Hey, you guys are
always stealing my ideas.
- We're monitoring
your mind, Joel.
Besides, in space, no
one can hear you sue.
Tell him, Frank.
- That's right.
We're evil, evil!
Those are just the most
delightfully cute creatures.
I want one like that.
I want a little
critter just like that.
I'm going to go to
the Hasbro humane--
- Frank!
- Huh?
- Your movie this week, Joel,
is not a science
fiction film,
but it's perfect
for our experiments.
It's just bad.
Tell him, Frank.
- That's right.
It's a diabolical cinematic,
it's just bad.
- Yes, remember that
bad thing we saw?
This is even worse than that.
- Yes.
That's right it's bad.
- But, it's our kind of bad.
It's a good bad.
- It's bad.
- It's good for us.
- Yeah.
- Bad for you, Joel.
- Ah, the movie's sign!
(alarm buzzing)
(doors creaking open)
Yeah, and those scientists,
they're always trying
to rip your head off.
- [Tom] Yeah, cheaters.
(motorcycle engines revving)
- Uh, this is gonna
be hard to watch.
- [Tom] Postage Stamp
Theater presents.
- Hey, they shot this with
a three millimeter camera.
- [Tom] I'd like
to shoot them
with a three
millimeter Howitzer.
- [Joel] Sidehackers?
- [Tom] Bigger, it's
got to be bigger!
- [Joel] Is that what
happens when a guy spits
out of the side of his mouth?
- [Tom] I think he's
going camera-free,
side-saddle on a horse.
- Oh, great, I
love orange soda.
- [Joel] I liked it
when they used to
shoot movies in
Orange Julius-scope.
(motorcycle engines roaring)
- [Tom] Well, they
can't be that good.
Look, they need
training wheels.
- Hey, the scientists
must be showing us ESPN.
Maybe they'll show kickboxing
from the Philippines.
(quick tempo
instrumental music)
- [Tom] Tonight's episode,
Bicycle Built for Death.
- Baby, can you
drive my murder?
- [Tom] These boots
were made for arson.
- [Joel] Two-wheeler,
four-wheeler, dead-wheeler.
- Easy rider, easy dead.
- [Tom] Tonight, act one,
with very special
guest, Ross Hagen.
- [Joel] And JC Hoffentopper,
tried off in two-sler.
- Hey, pretty snazzy track.
- [Tom] Couldn't you
do that in the privy?
Filmed in long torso vision.
- Hey, Dave Tessier,
hey the whole
Tessier clan got in on this.
- [Joel] You know, now
that sidehacking's so big,
it's really interesting
to see its humble origins.
♪ By the hard way ♪
♪ No easy time ♪
- Based on the award winning
stage play by Lillian Helman.
(chuckles)
- [Tom] Director
of blurriness,
Jon Hall and Erol
Hooks (chuckles).
- Hey, check
the map, will ya?
Why me, why me all the time?
- [Tom] Pat Somerset, bum.
That's what Mark Howard
used to do (chuckles).
- [Joel] And the Mike
Curb congregation.
- [Tom] Hey.
- And the rest.
- [Tom] Art director,
Lee Fischer.
- [Joel] Assistant camera
man, Vince Dyslexic.
- Assistant script
supervisor, Eddie Glaucoma.
- [Tom] Music editor,
uh, can't read it.
- [Joel] Hey,
let me up there.
- [Tom] That's no way
to kill hemorrhoids.
- My dog used to do
that on the driveway.
- [All] Oh, oh, ow, ow.
- [Joel] He was in
"Porgy and Bess".
- [Tom] No one's
legs were ground off
in the making of this film.
- I lost my contact, help me.
- [Joel] Help, I'm
sidehacking  and I can't get
up.
- I'm having butt pains.
- [Tom] Well, we'll be
right there Mr. Stumpy.
(crowd cheering)
There's that Jon Hall again.
- [Joel] She's happy.
- So, that's how Ross
Hagen got in the film,
he slept with the
producer (chuckles).
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Hunter S. Thompson.
I didn't know
sidehacking was so gonzo.
- [Tom] Yeah.
The winner's circle.
Full of burning tires.
- Hey, it used to be
a renaissance festival
as far as the eye can see.
- [Joel] Undercooked
pork by Gus Trikonis.
- Come on, let's go.
- [Tom] Meanwhile
in another movie.
- Hey, they're
filming a Kotex ad.
I'm a,
I can't say Kotex,
I'm a robot.
(chuckling)
- [Joel] Let's check in and
see what the Gatsbys are
doing.
- [Tom] Last one to the
montage is a rotten egg.
- Let's walk ankle
deep in filth.
- [Joel] So, what's so
bad about feeling good?
- [Tom] Haircut
by Chad Everett.
- Nope, nope (laughs).
- [Tom] You little tigress.
- They look like they're
filming a "Star Trek"
episode.
- [Tom] "Help me,
Kirk, help me.
"I am here, Rock."
- [Joel] Ah, life
is good, isn't it?
Our love is clean love.
- After we're married,
I still want this.
- [Tom] What, this tree?
- What do you mean?
- All being out here
where no one can bug us.
Just you and me.
- Oh, yeah, I love
that idea too.
- Yeah.
Hey, we think
alike, don't we?
- We both share a brain.
- Uh-huh.
- Hey, come here!
- [Tom] I'm going to break
your shin you little tigress.
(light orchestral music)
- Hey Joel, where do you
suppose these guys are
working now that
cigarette ads are illegal?
- [Joel] I don't know.
Maybe they're working
on "Peer Magazine".
- Oh.
- [Tom] Remember
when we were making
a film called Sidehackers?
- Now, let's see here.
You forgot your socks?
- No, silly, my underwear.
- Oh, you blew your nose?
- No, come on.
- Okay, what is it?
- [Joel] Uh, David McCellan's
coming over for dinner.
- Yep.
- I'm thinking that
you're the most
beautiful man in
the whole world.
- [Tom] I'm thinking
you're right.
- Come on,
I'm not beautiful.
- Well, you are.
- Yeah?
I can see why, honey.
- [Joel] And you
taste good too,
but your lips
are drugged, ahh.
Whoa.
- Hey, I'm tripping.
No, I'm really tripping.
Ouch, ouch there's a
protractor in my pocket.
- [Tom] Mystic
blinding effect,
and then we get
the bloom in the,
and sorry about my ham.
Lady, oh.
- Oh, come on, Jerry.
- [Tom] Mrs.
Morgan, himmy-hye.
- Oh, cut that out
Jerry and get off me.
- [Tom] Sorry about the
bugs and the keys, ow.
- Get your knee
out of my groin.
- [Tom] The best roll in the
hay I ever had (chuckles).
- [Joel] Oh, ow.
Ow, lady, ooh.
- [Tom] Even this grass is,
it's drugged!
- Had enough to eat?
- [Tom] I've grazed
enough, thank you.
- [Joel] I guess
we should talk now.
- But not of you.
Hmmm.
- [Tom] Hm, now do
that tiger noise again.
Growl.
- [Joel] Oh, love is good.
Love is good, yeah.
- Hmmm, Grum think love good.
- Want to guess what it is?
- [Tom] Nintendo?
Bunny?
- Fuel injection?
- Okay, let's see, a new car?
- [Tom] Next one
(imitates buzzer).
- You got two more guesses.
- [Tom] Pass
(imitates buzzer).
- Uh, sweater--
- [Tom] Pass.
- Come on, that's
more than two.
- Okay, what is it?
- It's a lock.
- [All] Aww.
- [Man] A what?
- You heard me, a lock.
- [Tom] A lock, you
know, a little fish,
you eat them on bagels.
- [Man] Now what am I
going to do with that?
- It's what I'm
going to do with it.
- Hm, I see.
What's that?
- I want you to
wear it, okay?
- In your septum.
- Okay.
- Hey, Luke?
So, she gave me this lock
like an engagement ring.
- So you had a good
time yesterday, huh?
- Yeah, sorry that you
and Lois couldn't make it.
- [Tom] Hey, why don't
you shut off that
motorcycle so we can talk?
- You really should have
some time to yourself.
You'll see what I mean
when the kids start coming.
- Yeah, it's funny, we
talked about that yesterday.
- [Luke] Yeah, you
sound like me when I was
about to take the big step.
- Yeah, what do you mean?
- Asking yourself
101 questions.
- [Joel] Can you
open the garage door?
- [Tom] Remember when
we used to be smart?
- When you finally do
it, it won't seem so big.
- [Rommel] Yeah, maybe.
(motorcycle engine revving)
- Look, you ever seen
me look so happy?
- [Joel] Yeah, but you didn't
know I was watching you.
- I've never seen
you looking so fat.
- Fat?
- Look.
- Yeah, I got to
start watching that.
- Well, family life's too
easy, makes a man soft.
You know what you
got to do, Luke?
Get out more, exercise.
- Exercise?
- Yeah.
- Well, I may be
soft, but I'm still--
- [Tom] Stupid.
(shouting)
Hya, hey, heya!
- Chop on the head
and the hook and a ho!
- [Man] Hellooo.
- [All] Hellooo.
- Am in time for
the main event?
- [Luke] What can
we do for you?
- Hey, it's Dick Sean.
- I got a bike that
needs some repairing.
- [Tom] Hey boss,
that's airplane glue.
- [Luke] We got a
couple ahead of you.
- Well, I got an exhibition
in Frisco in two weeks.
- [Joel] Then you won't
be needing those clothes.
- You think you can have
it ready by then?
- [Luke] Let's have a look.
- It's outside in the truck.
- [Joel] What, are you
coming on to me, hm?
- So, this must be what
they call a garage.
Cooky.
(upbeat jazz music)
- It's a nice
job you got here.
- [Rommel] Well, thanks.
- The way JC rides, he can
keep you in steady business.
- [Rommel] Oh,
what do you mean?
- Exhibition riding,
fairs, rodeos--
- [Tom] Weddings, bar
mitzvahs, you know.
- He can make a
bike do anything.
- [Joel] In fact, I'm a bike.
- I didn't get your name.
- Rommel.
- Oh, you magnificent
son of a bitch,
I read your book.
- No.
- You got a cigarette?
- [Joel] Got a dopey hat?
- No.
(chuckling)
- You think that's funny?
- You don't have
much to say, do you?
- No.
- [Tom] No.
- [Rommel] Are you
trying to say something?
- [Tom] No, no.
- No.
(chuckles)
- [Man] Paisly?
- [Tom] He looks
like Bud Freeman.
I hope he doesn't
try to hug everybody.
- What's with the
training wheels?
- It's called a sidehack.
- We built a whole
movie around it.
We had to pad up
that first scene with
metal, though.
- [Man] What's it for?
- We use it for racing.
You have a pilot
and a passenger.
It's up to the passenger to
balance out the bike on
corners.
Teamwork.
- I see, the guy rides
hanging onto this bar here.
- [All] D'oh!
- Where do you ride them?
- Well, we're having
some trials this weekend.
- [Joel] Hey, this whole
movie is a trial, all right?
(laughing)
- The sidehack, huh?
- [Tom] I like it!
- We can have it ready for
you  by the middle of next
week.
- Middle of the week, huh?
You told me two weeks, Nero.
What are you an
idiot or something?
- [Tom] Oh, you want
to give me some time
to think about that?
I don't know, maybe no.
- We'll see you next weekend.
This sidehack
thing I will see.
- [Tom] I will see it!
- Me too.
- Me three.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
(metal door closing)
- [Rommel] Now, weird
little guy, wasn't he?
- [Tom] Maybe he'll let
me call him Little Buddy.
- Did you invite him out?
- Yep.
- [Joel] Sure, I swing.
- Both ways?
- I thought you
left that all behind
when you bought the shop?
- Oh, sometimes you
talk like an old man.
Left all what behind?
- Trouble.
- [Tom] Right
here in the city.
- [Rommel] Now, what
do you mean by that?
- [Tom] Capital T, rhymes
with C, stands for chick.
- So what?
- So, that's no situation
to get yourself into.
He's bad news and
that's his old lady.
They're all nuts.
- [Tom] That little guy
in the mirror there.
- Fairs and rodeos and the
other half blowing their
mind.
- Oh, wow.
- The little lady comes
in here and starts
throwing her butt around.
Now, what am I
supposed to do?
Run in a corner and
hide or something?
- Get out of the
way of the butt.
- All right, forget
I said anything.
- All right, I will.
They come into here
and they want to
give us some business, right?
- Fine, but she's gonna
want some business too.
- Okay, but it's
not too bad, is it?
- So-so.
- [Tom] That's
what I'm asking.
- I don't know.
- [All] Third base.
- So-so, yes sir,
you may be married, Luke,
but your eyes aren't.
(door clicking)
- Guess who?
- Uh, are you known for
your work in the theater?
Tammy Grimes.
- Honey, do you
have some money?
The kids need new shoes.
- [Joel] Oh man, if
it's not one thing
it's another around here.
- Next, you'll be throwing
money at food and clothing.
- [Tom] Yeah, pick
me up a dime bag of
those (clears throat)
shoes, Colombian shoes.
- Why, Lois?
- [Tom] Eww.
- [Lois] Thanks.
- She brings by
lunch every day.
- [Tom] Well, it was
a tongue sandwich.
- You got it made, Luke.
- [Luke] It's okay,
your turn's coming.
- [Tom] Huh?
- Yeah, you want a cookie?
- [Luke] Hey,
that's my lunch.
(motorcycle engine revving)
- Interesting,
very interesting.
- [Tom] But stupid.
- How much racing
have you done?
- A little.
- That's what I
like about you.
Just give them enough
to make them wonder.
- That's right.
- Hey JC, where's your
next move after Frisco?
- Who knows, East, maybe.
- Thanks for littering.
God, what a pig.
- [Announcer] The California
Hackrace Competition.
A new and exciting sport
filled with thrills and
spills,
such as you've
never seen before.
- [Tom] And you
won't see now.
- Come on, come on, hurry up,
the film is slow enough.
- On hack number 14,
pilots Dan Shara,
Sharal, that is, and
passenger Dennis Wooly.
And on number five, Steve
Cant and his passenger--
- Jerry Mahoney.
- [Tom] How does she make
herself look like Buffy?
It's amazing.
- [Announcer] Pilot
Woody Splinter
and passenger Vince Rum who,
as I might add, our newcomer
in this thrilling new sport.
- [Tom] New newcomer
to this new sport?
Isn't that an oxymoron?
- [Joel] Known as Jerbingo.
- Hey, Jim Hutton.
- [Tom] His shin
bone's a muffler.
- [Tom] Brenda Fowler, Dolly
Fox, Wily Fort, Sandy Koufax.
- [Announcer] And on
hack number seven,
Crash Roach and his
passenger Jim McNeal.
- [Tom] Ruby Grape.
- Lefty Lemon.
- [Tom] Engine Orange.
- Jolly Olly Orange.
- [Tom] Loud Mouth Lock.
- Choo Choo Cherry.
- [Tom] Buffy, I'm sizzlin'.
- [Joel] And they
have no lines.
Hold me, please hold me.
- Oh, come on, Jerry.
- [Announcer] The
last three spills.
31, it's Joe Wheeler, showing
his lack of experience.
Oh, when you have
three wheels, baby,
use all three wheels.
- Hey, that announcer is way
too excited for his own good.
And for ours.
- [Tom] Pace
yourself, oh ham.
- [Announcer] Over
the second jump.
- [Joel] And the perma
crowd is in position.
- [Announcer] Spread over the
jumps, which the boys did.
It makes the jump safe.
I should say fairly safe.
And here they come
through the first jump.
Eddie Spencer with
his old beater.
He's still in the lead.
Second place, just
behind is Jeff Dean.
- [Joel] Jane, stop
this crazy thing.
- [Tom] I'm going
to throw up, argh.
- [Announcer]
Uh-oh, look out.
- Indy, throw me the whip.
- [Tom] Throw me the idol.
- The whip.
- [Tom] The idol.
All right, something
else is happening now.
Remember that other
thing I told you about?
It's happening again.
Oh no, now something, some
kind of stuff that's
different,
kind of different, but
it's the same kind of
similar stuff
happening in a way.
Oh look at that, some
more stuff's happening,
involving motorcycles
and a whole lot of dust.
This sport is so new we don't
even have the terminology
yet.
Oh, around the
clubhouse turn,
there's an apartment
house with plenty of room.
Girdle holds on
in the stretch.
And bottom up the
rear is Beetle Bum.
- [Announcer]
Smoothed out now.
Dean's dirt tractor
beating so much corruption.
Being so fast, I
can't even see.
- [Tom] I like my man best.
Mine's better.
- There's the team
from Footlocker.
- [Announcer] One
more left to go.
15 has moved up
to second place.
- [Tom] Just lean!
(imitates engine)
(coughing)
Come on, get back
in the frame.
You over there, back
in the frame, come on.
Get in here, get in there.
(light chiming music)
- [Joel] Good one,
Cambot, nice effect.
- [Tom] Whoa.
- [Announcer] And bike 16.
Inside gets fast.
The one and only,
he starts moving.
Okay, 20 still in this.
20 going, that's quite a kid.
- [Joel] For you folks
at home, this might be a
good time to go
get a sandwich.
(yawning)
- [Announcer] 15, hey, he's
stepping on the inside.
- [Tom] This is
exciting, isn't it?
- [Announcer] That
is the ultimate.
- Hey, you should have
gone before we left.
- [Joel] Here they come.
- [Announcer] Through
with a little action.
Buddy Drew's pulling up.
- [Joel] Come
on, we only live
through your
achievements, please.
- [Announcer] That's it.
All right, 22.
Oh, that's two
for Rommel fans.
- [Joel] Oh, we better
get out of here, you guys.
- [Tom] Thank Bob Crane for
being the flagman there.
- Oh, boy.
(doors slamming shut)
All right.
Well, we got a really
neat treat for you guys.
We've worked on some heavy
charts about sidehacking.
Cambot, I want you
to run the stat race
footage in there
on the chroma key.
Okay you guys, vamp.
Yeah, I'm trapped
up in outer space.
Sometimes, my life feels
like a big pile of nothing.
So what?
Word, I live with it, dig it.
But anyway, me and
my buds would like to
wail out a song about our
friends, the sidehackers.
It goes like this.
(upbeat music)
♪ Sidehacking is
the thing to do ♪
♪ And it doesn't hurt
to have a low IQ ♪
♪ Take your life, your
life, and a little luck ♪
♪ The big, grand
prize is 25 bucks ♪
♪ Sidehacking'll quench
your danger thirst ♪
♪ The stupid ones always
seem to come in first, yeah ♪
♪ Sidehacking is
one big bash ♪
♪ The favorite sport
of cheap white trash ♪
♪ When you're on your side,
make sure you don't slip ♪
♪ You'll end up with five
metal pins in your hip ♪
♪ Lean way back until
you scrape your butt ♪
♪ Make it look like a quarter
pound of ground chuck ♪
♪ Yeah, oh sidehacking Crow ♪
♪ Whooo ♪
- [Tom] Oh go, Crow.
♪ Some sport that attracts
a lot of racing fools ♪
♪ A lot of people get hurt
'cause there are no rules ♪
♪ All you need is
a toxic landfill ♪
♪ A cycle and a side car
and an urge to kill ♪
♪ Better get with this sport
'cause it won't last long ♪
♪ The founders of this sport
are laid at Forest Lawn ♪
(uptempo instrumental music)
(motorcycles revving)
- You guys were great.
The way you took
them on that corner,
I guess that'll bend them
out of shape for a while.
See, I like this
sidehack business.
You join me on the circuit.
I got some idea how to
put this into my act.
But you got to
build the drama.
See, that's what
you got to do.
You got to make
it look harder.
- All right, I'll wear
a porcupine costume.
- You want to try it?
- You're on.
- [All] Woohoo!
Woohoo, yeehoo.
Woohoo.
- Well, it's about this time
the ol' Duke boys decided to
show ol' Boss Hog what
sidehacking was all about.
- [Tom] Yeehoo.
So, you hurl them on
the ground and dosey-do,
make them sing
like a soprano.
Sidehack, yeah.
- Wow.
- [Tom] All right.
Yoohoo.
Then you fall off the
bike flat on your ass,
then you throw your butt
to the prairie grass.
You stick your
can up in the air,
and show us again
like you don't care.
Sidehack everybody.
Swing your sidehack.
- Let's go, Batman.
- [Tom] Yeehoo.
Well, you grab JC and
you swing him around,
you put him on the sidehack
and throw him down.
Sidehack, come on now.
Let's hear it for
Mr. Humility there.
Whoa.
Yeehoo, looks like a great
place for a sidehack, doesn't
it?
This is where
cows sidehack it.
Whoa, yeehoo.
Yee.
- [Joel] Thanks folks,
I'll be here all week.
Tip the waitress,
enjoy the buffet.
- [Tom] Yeehoo,
more of the same.
Whoa.
(grunting)
And this is my
country estate.
I also keep a trailer
home in the city.
(laughing)
- We did it.
- [Joel] We really are
having some fun, aren't we?
It's time for some
international coffee.
- What a trip!
- [Tom] Orange cappuccino?
- Hey, did you hire an
after dinner speaker?
- Groovy place.
How'd you get it?
- Luke and I bought it.
- We're going to live
here after we're married.
- [Tom] Rrrrr.
- [JC] A little love nest.
- Yes.
(laughing)
- It's a beautiful place.
- [Tom] Let's not
patronize him or anything.
- Isn't it a beautiful
place, honey?
- Yeah, it is.
- She's so articulate.
- You're joining
the establishment.
- [Tom] And the establishment
is plastic, man.
- Yep.
- Come on, Rommel,
why don't you
and the old lady
ride with us, huh?
We can make a lot of
money on this circuit.
- Hey, let me get you
another beer, huh?
- It looks like they're
drinking motor oil.
Oh, you should
never drink 10W30
in the summer.
- No one's along when
they're with JC.
- Hey, JC, I need to
ask you something.
- What are you
bugging me for?
- [Man] Whoa.
- [Tom] Say.
- [Man] He didn't
mean no harm.
- [Joel] Switch to decaf.
- Get your hands off me!
- [Joel] Oh, real nice.
- [All] Shut up.
(somber instrumental music)
- Woo, well, he
really sucked the
air out of that
room, didn't he?
Well, beamed up, anyone?
- [Tom] Let's kiss.
By hurting others, our
love grows stronger.
(exhaling)
That was fun.
- He just doesn't
want to, JC.
- [Joel] Hm, huh?
- What do you mean
doesn't want to?
- [Tom] Let's see,
does not want to,
which word didn't
you understand?
- Hm?
- (chuckles) Cookie face.
(imitates tongue
kissing noises)
- I'll try not
to beg you, man.
It's your choice.
- [Tom] Yeah, it is my
choice and I don't want to.
- [Joel] Sorry, bye now.
Capital day.
- Come on, let's go.
- [Tom] Hey, but I haven't
had any seven layer salad.
- Will you get out of here?
Well, thanks for
coming, now stay out.
- [Joel] Geez, what
does Martha Stewart
say about times like this?
- [Tom] Wait, that's
for the drug test, no.
Oh, darn.
- [Joel] Ah, really didn't
go too good, did it?
- Is there any intelligence
in that head of yours?
- [Tom] No wait,
wait, you asked me
that once before, I know.
- Whoopie.
- [Joel] Goldberg.
- One minute
accomplishment in a day.
He's dealing with idiots.
Now, if you can
answer me this one.
- Uh huh.
- [Tom] Riddle me this.
- Simple question, school
will be out for the day.
- Is this going to
be on the final?
- Attention, if
you came with me--
- [Tom] Mm-hmm, uh huh.
- Why shouldn't
Rommel come with me?
- [Tom] 'Cause he's
not your girlfriend?
- Hey, baby, you were my
meal ticket out of that town.
- What's with this
meal ticket bit?
- [Tom] Chicago?
- I saved you from
a life of nothing.
- I bet you'd like
to believe that.
I don't know what I saw
in you in the first place.
It would have been a lot more
exciting to take the bus.
- Yeah, but then
you'd have to
sit next to the stinky guy.
- [Paisly] Oh man,
you should have s
een yourself
being drug around.
Rommel had you looking like
an overstuffed Polish
sausage.
(laughing)
- [Tom] But I am a thuringer.
- Ah, you're nothing
but a little boy, JC.
You disappoint me
all the way around.
(Tom clears throat)
- I never disappointed
you in bed.
(clears throat)
(whistles)
- Really?
- Don't walk away when
I'm talking to you, Pais.
- Get your hands off me.
- You damn dirty ape.
- Scream for your loverboy?
Go ahead, scream, I
want to hear you scream.
Scream.
- Please, JC.
- [Tom] Do we have
to watch this?
- Not, until you scream,
now scream.
- [Joel] What a creep.
- Help.
(slapping and punching)
- [Joel] Oh, hey.
That's it, that's it.
- Boo, boo, no.
- [Joel] Oh, boy.
- Come on, Pais.
You hear me, baby?
You're mine, every mother
loving inch of you.
- [Tom] But, I can't breath.
- If anybody touched
you, I'd kill them, Pais.
That's how much
I love you, baby.
- Oh, I guess he
really does love her.
- [Tom] He kind of
kisses like a dog.
- I'm sorry, baby.
We're a team, sweetheart.
- [Joel] Yeah, I'm
Punch and you're Judy.
- I'll prove it to you, baby.
- [Tom] Try some of
my forbidden fruit.
- Come on.
- An apple a day--
- [Luke] It says
three o' clock--
- [Tom] Good thing
he's using that mask
to protect his scalp.
- I can't get this
sparkler to light, Hal.
And he really go and
he gets the gas tank.
- [Luke] Hey Rommel,
you like those
chubby checkers
that Lois gets?
- Yeah, yeah, but
they burn my gut.
- [Tom] Yeah,
like this movie.
- But I think that's
what Rita and Lois are
making for dinner tonight.
(chuckling)
- How come every time we
go to the ranch, Luke,
we got to have chili peppers?
Why not hamburgers?
You know I love hamburgers.
- Less talk, more move.
- [Joel] Hey, what's
the director doing here?
- It's ready.
- Good.
- Now open the garage door.
It's show time.
- How much?
- 32 bucks.
- [Tom] Boy, this
is a cheap movie.
- Hey Luke, did you pick up
those parts for the Harley
yet?
- I'll get them now.
You want a sandwich?
- Yeah, one with
everything on it.
- [Tom] Mm-hmm.
Mmm, good.
(uptempo instrumental music)
- [Joel] That refrigerator's
been everywhere.
- And so has she.
- [Joel] Mm-hmm.
- Hi.
- [Tom] Uh, why yes I
am, I'm on a ladder.
- How you doing?
- Good.
- [Tom] Better than you.
- Where's your buddy?
- Kind of personal, isn't it?
- [Rommel] Oh, he
went for some parts.
- Oh?
- [Rommel] What's up?
- I just thought I'd stop by
and see if you've
changed your mind.
- Running errands
for the old man, huh?
- You might call it that.
- [Joel] I call
it co-dependency.
- It's just that
he doesn't like
being turned down.
- Yeah, well life's full
of little rejections.
- [Tom] Oh, like my rejection
from Simon and Schuster when
my book came out.
- I know what you mean.
- I've read your book you
magnificent (clears throat).
- Can you use some
help over there?
- [Tom] Oh yeah, you
could button me up.
- Hand me that box there.
- [Joel] Now,
quack like a duck.
- Ow.
- Here, let me get it.
- I had fun yesterday.
You were great.
- Thanks.
You know, JC's not bad, a
little funny but not bad.
- [Joel] He's no
Gallagher or anything.
- Rommel?
- [Tom] You
magnificent son of a--
- Do you like me?
- [Rommel] Well sure,
I like everybody.
- [Joel] I even like
Gallagher for crying out
loud.
- Then why do you back off
when I try to
get close to you?
- There's a
ladder in the way.
- You know, I
can't get to you.
- There's a
ladder in the way.
- Why not?
- Now, look Paisley,
you got a man, right?
- Maybe I'd like a change.
- [Tom] Maybe she's got a
saggy diaper that leaks.
- [Rommel] Yeah, what do
you want me to do about it?
- [Joel] I thought
maybe you knew someone.
- You and me.
- Look, Paisley, you
go on home and grow up.
You know, that's the nice
thing about a little girl.
If they're lucky, they
can grow up to be women.
- You bastard.
I'm more of a
woman than you'll
ever know, you
son of a bitch.
- Uh, that's magnificent
- What's she uptight about?
- [Joel] I don't know,
I just don't get girls.
- [Tom] Hey, I asked for a
bagel and a shmear, what's
this?
- Don't give me
no pilatski, huh?
- Okay, and this is his bike.
I want you to
take a look at it.
- Hey, I got to take the
fridge to the airport,
you need anything?
- It's right outside here.
- [Rommel] Hey, Nero,
you got problems?
- [Joel] Yeah,
Rome's burning, why?
- [Nero] I was on my way
out of town when
misfortune struck me,
and I think I burned
the internal combustion
off my engine.
- [Luke] That is a problem.
- Yes, sir, indeed it is.
- I got to thinking about
that work we discussed,
if the offer's still open.
- Yeah, I think we can
work it out for you.
- Sure.
(imitating crying)
- [Tom] Turns out
they really wanted
Nancy Sinatra for this role.
Maybe my boots were
made for walking
right off of this set,
then I go and spoil
it all by saying something
stupid like, I love you.
- I feel like I'm
time tripping.
That Buffy girl got to stand
next to Jim Huppin look
alike.
- [Tom] I remember it all.
I remember the way he used to
snap his jacket off for me.
- [Joel] And I remember
that too, that's worse.
- [Rommel] You go
on home and grow up.
That's the nice thing
about little girls.
- [Tom] Remember the
way Rommel insulted me?
And the way JC made
me cough up blood.
You can't take those precious
memories away from me.
(imitates crying)
- [Joel] Take that, Nancy
Sinatra (imitates crying).
- Hey, Luke?
- What?
- [Joel] All done in there?
- Just wondered if you
and Lois and the kids were
going to stay at the ranch
tonight after we eat dinner.
- Well, we were
thinking about it.
Why?
- Oh no, I was
just wondering.
- [Tom] Aha, turn up.
- What were you wondering?
- [Joel] Oh, just wondering.
- Nothing.
- [Joel] Yeah, nothing.
- You and Rita want to stay
up by yourselves tonight?
- [Tom] Bingo.
- Well, that's a
good idea, Luke.
- [Joel] Kind
of read my mind.
- You sure you don't mind?
- No problem.
- Thanks.
- [Tom] Nope,
don't mind at all.
- You just gonna sit out
there and relax tonight, huh?
- [Joel] This is kinda
looking like 30 Something.
- Yeah, except for the dirty
pictures in the background.
- [Tom] Yep, uh huh.
- Then?
- I'm going to put
my arm around her.
(chuckling)
- Yep.
- Well, like I said,
you and Rita should
have some time to yourselves.
- [Tom] Yeah, time.
- Hey, you know,
you're right, Luke.
- [Tom] Need some more time.
- [Joel] Yeah, time.
- Then what?
- [Tom] Oh, you know, I'm
going to give her a kiss.
(goofy laughing)
(slow romantic music)
- [Tom] Mmm, so soft, mmm.
- You sure you want--
- That's a lovely
dress she's wearing.
- How do you plan
to have 100 kids?
- [Tom] Huh?
- Moments like this here.
- [Joel] What?
- [Joel] Oh,
there's really a ton
of change in this mattress.
- Are you going to
take care of them all?
(laughing)
- Turn you into
a widow woman.
(mumbling)
- Nice vaccination scar.
- Into a widow woman, huh?
- [Tom] Widow woman.
(grumbling)
- Widow woman ain't too bad.
Especially those ones that--
- [Tom] It's Rod
Stewart and Kim Carnes
in Laryngitis Theater.
- Come on, Ricky, the
ceiling needs painting, ahh.
- You still love me?
(grumbling)
- [Joel] Ugh, this guy's
really got a hairy back.
- [Tom] Yikes.
Look, he's kissing
himself now.
- Why?
- [Joel] I just
imagined you at 90 and
I don't think I can
do this anymore.
(blows raspberries)
(laughing)
- [Joel] Hm, ha ha ha, good.
Take a big drink out of life.
- Sounds like the
start of sidehack film.
- [Tom] Sounds like they're
sharing the same larynx.
- Make my bed.
- Mm-mm, I threw
cold water on Batman.
(laughing)
- [Joel] I think she's
laying on a lamp shade.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [All] Hello, Sheriff.
- What happened?
- Rommel.
- [Man] I know where he is.
- Algeria.
- [Man] I heard him
tell his buddy he was
going to the cabin
where we had the party.
- Cooch, stay with her.
You guys, come with me.
- [Tom] Isn't it Gooch?
- You know, Rom, I
really love this place?
- [Tom] Hm, this place, hm.
- After we get married,
I'm going to fix it up.
(grumbling)
All it really needs
is a woman's touch.
- [Tom] Yeah,
like I care, yeah.
- I'm going to
stain the walls.
- [Joel] Oh, yeah.
- Maybe to give it a bit
of a fresh, clean look.
- Yeah, we're stained, yeah.
- We'll get blue draperies
to match my blue, blue couch.
- [Joel] Mm, yeah, you know
what I could do with that.
It would cost a fortune.
- And throw rugs, throw
rugs all over the place.
- [Tom] Yeah, throw up
on those throw rugs.
Yeah.
- A couple of new lamps, huh?
- [Joel] Yeah, like the
ones you were laying on.
- [Tom] Why don't you
just take my wallet.
(imitates snoring)
- I'll pick fresh
flowers every day.
- [Tom] Lillies.
Oh my God, so many other
women in my life
I could have...
- You think I'm being silly?
(imitates snoring)
Rom?
(smacks lips)
- [Tom] Patton's here,
Patton's here, honey.
Wake up you desert fox, you.
(imitates kissing)
- I love you.
- [Joel] Hm, yeah right.
- [Tom] Sure, whatever.
- I love you.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Tom] Let's go.
- [Joel] We better
get out of here.
- [Tom] I'm tired of her.
- Time's up, lover boy.
Get him.
(uptempo instrumental music)
- Joel, what happened,
where'd the sidehacking go?
- Yeah, where'd it
go, we liked it.
- Well, you guys
got to understand,
it's really hard to
get a new sport going.
It's hard to get the
recognition that other sports
enjoy.
Can you name a few?
- Uh, kickboxing
from the Philippines.
Uh, tape measure racing.
- And computations, and
Australian rules football.
- Right, and what do all
these sports have in common
that sidehacking does not?
- A rudimentary
interest factor.
- A sense of fair play.
- A small measure
of self-esteem?
- Yeah.
- Right, these are all
really good answers,
but the thing I was looking
for was terminology.
It's impossible to
have play by play
or color commentary
without it.
So, let's put our heads
together and come up with
some terminology that
showcases some of the
really exciting moves in
our sport, sidehacking.
Cambot, roll that footage.
- [Crow] It looks like
the Wesley brothers
out of John Harding
starting things briskly
with the fuller brush man
and a Rumplestiltskins
follow through
with a teenage co-ed prison.
- [Tom] Out of Warsaw
representing Wisconsin,
Mitch and Pitch
now performing the
now famous Yank Me, Crank Me.
- [Joel] That bright young
teen, the Allentown Poodles,
with their rendition
of the swirly.
Oh no, could that have
been the gunk out?
Crow?
- [Crow] Thanks, Joel.
I think that was more of
a spinning love funnel
from those fresh face kids of
Kankakee Community College.
- [Tom] Oh my goodness, it's
a line back, a small burn,
and a hop, skip and
a go lane with a
ventusler and a vinci
gorilla, a vinci gorilla.
- [Joel] Uh oh, here
comes the big blue flamer
followed by tea
time, Richard Scarry,
the full tilled bozo crazy
and just plain stupid.
- [Crow] It's an exciting
day indeed here at
Japanese War Atrocity Park
and Pavilion on the park.
But what's this?
Is that the antiquated
old Puffa Bobba O'Reilly
attempting the Teenage
Wasteland on the
heidy hidey hoe
side of the track?
- [Tom] From the darker
side of the street,
come the Cat's Nap Crew,
Maynard and Eleanor,
Casey's rolling
pizza, I just imagine.
- [Joel] Meet you on the
dark side of the moon.
It's the ghostly trio
followed by No-Tell Motel,
Ask For Cream and
Death by Chocolate.
- [Crow] Oh, hold on
to your epidermis,
it's Deputy Dog and the hard
drinking soldiers of fortune
attempting the Off
Copy Leaky Tease.
- [Tom] Shake me
to wake me, Crow,
it looks like Batman and the
Costume Critters of Death
are going crinkle cut and
somebody's got to pay.
But uh oh, funny ha
ha, funny strange,
at the Batman in tow
screaming, hey world, check me
out.
- [Joel] Hand me over,
it's Raspberry Commie,
the Fruitful Snootful
and Hickory Dickory Dye
attempting a
Butterscotch Push with a
Frunky, Frunky, Frunky.
- [Crow] Ho ho ho, is
that GoGo the Gorilla with
bloopers, blunders,
and practical jokes
with Starchy Cuck
and the wock and
their fintusler.
There's Electrowoman
and Dina Girl in the
George Barris custom show
rod, bravely attempting the
Big Guy with a Tommy
Tune on the side.
- [Tom] I've got to
correct you on that, Crow.
I think he's attempting the
Stinky Guy with a Pete Allen.
Uh oh, that means he'll be
disqualified and slept with a
day in the life of
Eva Danisivitch.
That could be a problem
for our Quentin Crisp,
who's expected to
deliver a fighting
out of its brother or a,
God, your helmet smells good.
- [Joel] Uh oh, here comes
Nutsy the sidehacking clown
performing his famous
tension envelope routine.
Don't get too close
'cause remember, kids,
he who smelt it dealt it.
Let's give him a
round of applause as
we all pardon his blooper.
- Well, it's been a
big day with plenty of
shared gut blow
outs, Juicy Lucy's,
and a woozahoola
who's name was Peanut.
This is Crow, and Joel,
and Tom Servo in the pit.
We'll be at the 19th
quadrant attempting a
grass grinder and
ground grass as a
mulching mulch is
good for your lawn.
- That ought to hold it.
(alarm buzzing)
- [All] Oh, we
have movie sign.
(doors opening)
- [Tom] Say, the
excitement, the action.
- Oh, thank you.
- [Joel] Oh, you
got a little--
- [Tom] You got a little
on your cheek there.
- Oh, that jelly doughnut
kind of got away from him.
- [Tom] I got a feeling.
(mysterious
instrumental music)
Oh.
- [Joel] Oh no.
- At least my car's okay.
- [Tom] Oh no, they
stole his radio.
(mysterious
instrumental music)
- Oh, they stole
his kneecaps.
- [Tom] Is it safe?
It's not safe.
Now, he's safe.
- [Joel] I got to call
my agent and try to
get a hold of (mumbling).
- They stole his dimes.
- [Tom] Oh, and they
stole the camera dolly.
It isn't safe, it isn't safe.
- They stole the
shoulder of the road.
- [Joel] Must find
a dry cleaners.
Got to (groans).
- Hey, hey stop, stop I
need a new girlfriend.
(car horn honking)
- [Tom] Oh, thanks anyway.
There's probably another
car over the hill.
Okay.
(imitates crying)
Mom, dad?
I don't want to be a
grownup sidehacker anymore.
(imitates crying)
- [Woman] Sure, Luke.
- Rommel.
What the hell
happened to you?
- It was Patton,
he read my book.
- Rommel?
- [Tom] Well, hate to
bleed and run but--
- [Luke] Rommel, come back!
- [Joel] You magnificent,
oh, let him go.
- [Tom] Oh, I can
talk to you Mr. Tree.
- [Joel] Oh magic lock,
take me to the freeway.
("Only Love" by The New Life)
♪ I'm head over heels ♪
- [Joel] Poor guy.
- Rita used to like
coming to the highway.
(imitates crying)
- [Tom] I need another
band-aid for my broken heart.
(imitates crying)
- We used to come here
and club seals together.
(imitates crying)
- [Joel] Oh and even
these oil fields seem
to remind me of her.
I can't put my finger on it.
♪ But nothing lasts forever ♪
(humming along to music)
♪ Only love,
that's the fields ♪
- [Joel] I think I look like
Robert Conway, don't you?
♪ All between ♪
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Only love ♪
♪ That's the fields ♪
- For those of you playing
along at home, Rita is dead.
- [Tom] Right.
♪ The friends that you make ♪
(panting)
- [Joel] Oh, who
am I trying to kid?
It's no fun without a girl.
♪ You live all you can ♪
♪ A day in the sun ♪
♪ But even the sun ♪
♪ Must descend ♪
- [Tom] I'm making this up.
♪ But nothing lasts forever ♪
- They used to sit there.
♪ Only love ♪
♪ That's the field ♪
- Oh, I looked at this
already, I forgot.
(chuckles) Cookie.
- [Tom] Hey, I'm
getting over it already.
Just 'cause she was
murdered, brutally murdered.
(imitates crying)
- Cramped up in this
lousy motel for two weeks.
I got to get out, I
can't breathe, Gooch.
- [Tom] Hey look,
I'm a mirror,
I can't talk.
- A second longer the
cops are bound to find me.
Look for a place I can hide.
The mountains, maybe.
- Make a reservation
at Grossinger's.
- Just get me out!
- [Tom] Whoa.
- No one will find me here,
I'll climb in
a corner pocket.
- What are you
planning to do?
- [Joel] Eight
ball, corner pocket.
What would you do?
- [Tom] No, I'm in there.
- Kill him.
- [Tom] I will kill him!
- We talked to the
police and they're
out looking for JC now.
- [Tom] And some
call them pig.
- It's their job, Rommel,
let them handle it.
- It may be their job, but
what have they done so far?
Nothing.
- [Tom] Well, there's
the roads, highways.
- Yeah.
- You've got to
snap out of it.
- You've been playing
nine ball all day,
play air hockey.
- Why don't you
come back to work
so you can get your
mind off of it?
- You ever read
the Bible, Luke?
- No, but I saw the movie.
- There's an old passage
about an eye for an eye.
- [Joel] I'm not much
for the classics.
I've only read your book
you magnificent bastard.
- You ever read that one?
- They're going to
bust you wide open.
- Let me think about that.
- Like a pinata.
- It contradicts itself.
One minute it tells you
to turn the other cheek,
then it tells you
to take an eye.
- [Tom] Well, that's when
you run out of cheeks.
- I guess it depends
on which end you read.
- [Tom] If you
start from the back,
it's even more confusing.
- Rommel.
- You didn't have your
feet on the floor.
- There's nothing
you can do about it.
- Like I said, depends
on which end you read.
(imitates squeaking)
- [Tom] I guess
pool is the answer.
I don't worry about my
girlfriend's murder.
Eight ball, corner pocket.
- [Joel] Hey, you know, I'm
playing my way through my
grief.
Every shot I get
better and better.
- Now since this film
isn't going anywhere,
why don't we all play pool?
- [Tom] Hmm?
Huh?
- [Joel] Say--
- I found a couple of boys.
They're willing
to ride with us,
but there's one
little problem.
- [Tom] One of them's six
years old and the other's 11.
- They're short on funds.
They don't care what they do,
as long as they
get paid for it.
- I need some money.
- [Luke] What for?
- [Joel] To finish
these monkey bars.
- I'm buying myself
a little help.
- [Tom] You thought
about county girls?
- Still going to
go after JC, huh?
- Pdq, asap.
- But, if you
think I'm going to
finance your
war, you're nuts.
- [Joel] It just may work.
- Hey, Luke, come on now,
we want to talk to you.
- [Tom] Right over here,
director wants to
do another set up.
Come on, see what I mean?
- I'll give you the note
to my part of the shop
so that if anything
happens to me,
you can still get
your money back.
- I don't give a damn about
your part of the shop.
If anything happened to you,
your part of the shop
wouldn't mean a thing.
Now look, you can go
fussing and hollering all--
- How come they
get louder as they
get closer to the camera?
- Now either you help me
or I'll be looking
someplace else.
- Well, I'm afraid
you're going to
have to look someplace else.
- [Tom] Taxi, tax--?
Oh, I drove, I forgot.
(light rock music)
(car horn honking)
- [Joel] Okay, that's
I go to the bank,
I go to the dry
cleaners, get some lunch,
kill JC's gang--
- [Tom] Salvage
the film here.
- Why doesn't he
just sell his car?
- [Tom] This is the
vengeance music.
- [Man] What
can I do for you?
- I ran a little
short this month.
Give you a good
deal on some tools.
- Don't need them.
- [Joel] They're
not for eating.
- They're worth 50 bucks.
I'll let you
have them for 35.
- [Man] I just
don't need them.
- [Tom] He said you're
not supposed to eat them.
- 25 and I'll throw
in my spare tire.
- - [Joel] Why didn't
you just say tires?
We love tires.
- Now, I'll give
you $5 if you have
a hard-boilded
egg in your purse.
- You got a 10?
- Yeah, I got a 10.
- [Joel] You got a
pretty nice tan yourself,
brother of mine.
- [Tom] Been in
the trunk awhile.
- With what you're paying?
I wouldn't sweat it.
- [Joel] A little warm.
- All I got is 10s.
- Give me those.
- Thanks.
- [All] Not.
- Now Jake, that's
all the man's got.
And I gave him my word.
But $200 I
wouldn't even move.
- I couldn't.
- Now, Jake, man to man.
- [Joel] I don't even
know what he said.
- Why, thank you.
- [Jake] Did you ever see
Big Jake break a man's back?
- [Tom] No, but once I saw
a bear drinking a soda.
- [Joel] Uh oh.
- You hit me.
- [Tom] Yep, sure did.
- Did you see what he did?
- [Tom] Yeah, he hit you.
- I saw the whole
thing, what happened.
- [Tom] Yep.
- He hit Big Jake.
- [Tom] Yeah, he hit him.
If you're Big
Jake, you got hit.
- I ought to break your back!
- Oh, ow, you
crushed my sternum,
you made me sit
on a hard thing,
it's hot and it
hurts and stuff, ow.
- [Jake] When do we start?
- [Joel] Is this
your way of haggling?
- Two, three days at
the most (coughs).
- [Man] Look, I said
I'd give you $200.
- [Tom] What is she, oh.
- [Joel] It is massive.
- Always work these
brushes into a fine point.
- You could kill
a man with them.
- It helps bring out
the detail in my work.
- [Joel] He's going
to hire a painter?
- Will that bring Rita back?
Paint a picture of her.
- [Joel] It'll last longer.
- That's as close as you're
ever going to get to her
again.
- Rita?
Oh yeah, dead
girlfriend, right, right.
- She's gone.
- [Tom] Oh, I'd pay the
devil to replace her.
- Another time,
another place.
- Dead, bloated,
worm food, you know.
- We don't have to worry
about  our hangups here
anymore.
- - [Joel] Okay,
okay, note to myself,
don't talk to an artist.
- All they got time to know
and understand is themselves.
- Uh, so is that a yes?
- What you got?
- You don't want
her here, do you?
People find their
own bag, get in it.
- [Tom] Here's my
bag under here, oh.
- [Tom] Whoa.
- Yep.
- [Joel] Hey, how did
the laughing audition go?
- [JC] You're saying he's
coming after me by himself?
- Yeah, and the word is out
he's buying
himself some help.
He doesn't think the
law is doing its job.
- Who, who's he buying?
- Nero, two and three others.
- [Tom] A pop of a pauper,
a pawn, and a king.
Each time he finds
himself flat on his face.
Oh, you know the rest.
- That Rommel, he just don't
learn too easy, does he?
I gave him the light, man.
- [Joel] And he just
kept doing time.
- I tried to
show him the way.
I was like a brother to him.
- Not a good brother.
- Now Cooch, Cooch tell me--
- [Tom] It's Gooch.
- Did I love Rommel?
Hm, did I love him?
My own flesh I
don't love better!
- [Joel] He gets this way if
he doesn't kill every day.
- I'm not good
enough for him.
How many times did I
ask him to ride with me?
- [Tom] You got a
little up there, man.
- He says, "No."
- [Tom] Oh mama.
- Could be he's trying to
bring me out in the open.
We'll see what kind
of game he's playing.
- [Tom] Othello,
Hungry Hungry Hippo,
Shoots and Ladders,
Candy Land, maybe?
Uh, Mil Borne, Uno, Monopoly,
Risk, Trivial Pursuit?
- [Joel] Oh, you're so tense.
(imitates sensual music)
- We get rid of him, then
there's no witnesses.
- JC, we've had
enough trouble.
Please, let's just
get out of here.
- You dare mock me?
- He tries to put the make
on you so I paid him back!
How'd I know she
was going to die?
- [Tom] Uh, 'cause
you killed her.
- Ain't that right, honey?
Tell me, ain't it right?
- Can you repeat the
question please, Peter?
- Damn you all to hell!
(imitates kissing)
- [Joel] Uh, yeah,
everything's better now, hurt
is gone.
- I want you to get
ahold of the other boys.
Tell them to meet me
here, to bring guns,
whatever they can
get their hands on.
- [Tom] Wear in loose
fitting clothes,
dress to move, have a
two-minute song prepared.
- Gooch, Gooch come here.
- That's Cooch, sir.
- Sit down.
- Take your shoes
off, sit a spell.
- I trust you, my
friend, I trust you.
We've had a lot
of runs together.
- [Joel] Yeah, remember
that dinner in Tijuana?
- [Tom] Oh, I made a run
for the border that night,
my little compadre.
- You always stick by me.
Now, I need you, Gooch.
I want him.
- [Joel] You need
me, but you want him?
- Yeah, I'll get him.
- No, you got to get in
and you bring Rommel to me.
- Yeah, I will.
- [Joel] I will do it.
- But it's got to look right.
- [Joel] I will.
- Let him know
where I'm hiding.
- I will.
- [Joel] I will do it.
- Make him think you
would ask for this.
- [Joel] I am, okay, I will.
- But baby, its
got to look right.
- You know I'd do
anything for you, JC.
- [Joel] Would
you kill a guy?
- Anything.
- Fine, I know.
- [Joel] I'll do it.
(punching)
- [Tom] And so they drove
to the power station
and there was nothing
left of the world
after the Robot Holocaust.
♪ I know a wiener man,
he owns a hot dog stand ♪
♪ He gives me anything
from wieners ♪
- Key change.
- [Tom] Where'd
you say he was?
He must have forgot
we're going after him.
- [Joel] PCH.
- [Tom] Oh, look at the
moon, it must be dark out.
(imitates howling)
Oh, look how dark
it is tonight.
- It's really something.
- [Joel] And the crickets?
Yeah, add some crickets.
- If it was dark you could.
(imitates crickets)
Hey, I said left
at the Dairy Queen.
I guess it was too dark.
- [Joel] They don't even
have their lights on.
- [Tom] It's so dark out,
they don't need their
lights, I guess.
- They're breaking the law.
- [Joel] See,
once I kill a guy,
then this'll become
a sidehack track.
What do you think?
- [Tom] That's nice.
- Hey Gooch, what's the deal?
- We better wait
here 'till morning.
- [Tom] Yeah, it's too dark
now, can't see a thing.
That's why I'm squinting.
- Why not tonight?
- I'm too tired.
- You know, JC
likes his booze.
- [Tom] Loves
to have his fun.
- You hit him in the morning,
he won't know what happens.
- Or that means he'll be
really drunk right now,
right?
- (sighs) What can I say?
- [Tom] How about, I'm sorry?
(dramatic orchestral music)
- Well, I still think
we should go under the
cloak of darkness but,
we'll do it your way.
- [Tom] It's so dark
out tonight, I mean--
- Yeah, I'm glad it's dark.
You can't tell my hat
looks like Jiffy Pop.
- [Joel] Hey, his hat
looks like Jiffy Pop too.
Buttered and un-buttered.
- Please, Luke, don't do it.
- Honey.
Lois, go back in the house.
- We'll call the
police from here.
- Honey, I owe Rommel more
than a call to the police.
- [All] What?
- What about me and the kids?
- [Tom] The kids
can come too.
- Bring their jammies,
put them on the
top of the car.
- It's too
dangerous, don't go.
- [Joel] Billy,
don't be a hero.
- [Tom] Hey look,
he's sporting a woody.
- [Joel] Yeah,
classic styling.
- Welp bye, honey.
Don't wait up, I'll be dead.
- [Tom] Write
if you get work.
- Hey, turn your lights on.
- [Tom] It's dark
out, remember?
It's dark.
- Idiot.
- This ol' boy
got thirsty, see?
And he gets tossed
into Sing Sing.
Now, the first
night he's there,
his cellmate walks
over to the bars
and he yells out,
"Number nine!"
- [Joel] Oh, not this--
- [Tom] Yeah, we know,
you can't tell people
you can't tell a joke, yeah.
I loath him.
- Number 12!
And the whole place
wakes up again, see?
So, this new boy turns to
his cellmate and he says,
"Hey, man, what is
with this number bit?"
So, the old con
tells him, he says,
"That's the way we tell
jokes around here."
Now, everybody here
knows every joke,
so we just give
them a number.
- [Tom] Yeah, yeah
we know, we know.
- And when we feel like
telling a joke, we just
yell out a number, see?
- [Joel] Yeah, I heard
Tipadada used to do a
number one that
was a killing.
- This new boy
decides he's going to
tell himself a joke, see?
- Yawn.
- So, he walks up to the bars
and he yells out,
"Number eight!"
(all laughing)
- Oh, I get it.
- [Joel] Oh wait,
that's not it.
- [Tom] Oh, that's
not the punchline?
- [Joel] No.
- Not a peep out
of the cellblock.
- [Joel] There's more.
- I mean, don't nobody laugh.
Well, he turns to the
old con and he says--
- [Tom] Just kill
this guy for practice.
- "Hey, man, how
come nobody laughed?"
(laughing)
- Maybe 'cause
it wasn't funny.
- [Joel] Oh, how I loath him.
- So, the old con looked
at him and he says--
- [Joel] I know
what you mean.
- [Man] And he says--
- [Joel] Just keep listening.
I'll try to make
the most of it.
- [Man] He says, he says--
- [Joel] He's not half bad.
(laughing)
- [Tom] Keep him talking,
I'll hit him over the head
with a rock.
- "Let's face it, boy,
"some people can tell
a joke and some can't."
- [All] And you can't.
- Hey, say, did you
ever hear the one about
the fag and the shaved dog?
- [All] Huh, what?
- [Man] Shaved dog?
Man, you putting
me on, ain't ya?
- No, no this guy
comes in a bar,
to borrow his dog, see--
- [Man] Is that the one
where the dog pins the
bartender to the
floor and he says,
"Bowsy wowsy"?
- [Tom] No, he says,
"Who shot my paw?"
- Yeah I did, I
remember it, bah!
How about that?
- Did you ever hear about
the stupid hillbilly
that got killed in the
dessert  by a bunch of bad
guys?
- [Tom] The one with
the big stick, right?
- Yeah.
- If Nero here rides with me,
I'm going to hold this
pole out like here, see,
just like a white knight.
- [Joel] I prefer
observation humor.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- I say the best
way is hand to hand.
Hit him hard and fast.
- [Tom] Hand to mouth.
- If you was built like
me you wouldn't say that.
- Like a tree frog?
- Remember what
Rommel said, no guns.
- [Tom] Yeah, that wasn't a
good policy for the German
army.
- What's the matter, Gooch?
Afraid to die?
- [Tom] A little.
- Who needs them?
- Me, that's who.
Suppose that JC's
sitting down there
with a little army.
- [Joel] A little
plastic army?
Those plastic army men?
- There's no way for
him to move, no way.
- Yes way.
- Us or the law gets him.
- Maybe you got a
better way, huh?
- [Joel] Well, yes I do, I
happen to have a lot of
ideas.
I've catered many of
these events before
and you'd be surprised
of the provocative
and useful ideas you
can come up with.
- Hey, Rommel boy?
- [Tom] Yes rock
stupid hillbilly boy?
- [Man] What if this
JC's sitting down there
with a little army?
- Uh, promise no more jokes
and I'll tell you
what you want to know.
- How many boys does he have?
- [Tom] It's Gooch, Gooch.
- Nothing to worry about.
- Nothing to
worry about, huh?
- [Joel] What about
the Middle East crisis?
That's got to bother
you a little bit.
- Yeah.
- I figure JC's going to be
sitting down there
waiting for us.
I think he knows when
we're coming too.
What we got to do is
sneak in and grab him.
Once I got JC,
there's no reason
for his boys to fight us.
- Unless they want him back.
- [Rommel] Jake and
me will go down first.
- [Tom] You,
you'll die later.
- [Crapa] What are
you going to do
when you get your
hands on him?
- I'm still
thinking about it.
- [Crapa] What if you don't?
- [Man] Yeah, now suppose
he grabs you first?
- Then you lead.
- Well then, you boys are
going to earn your money.
Crapa, you and
Gooch take the side.
- [Tom] Crapper?
- [Crapa] Hey, Rom?
I had this idea about using
this pole as a battering ram.
- [Joel] Good one.
- We were thinking
of using it as a
suppository on you.
- You come in from
the back side.
Cause as much
confusion as you can.
- [Joel] So,
what else is new?
- [Tom] Do that
stupid joke of yours,
that ought to hold them.
- Gooch, you play it by ear.
- Then betray us.
- [Crapa] Just wait a
minute, Rommel, boy,
what the hell are we
gonna do if they got guns?
- [Joel] Die, I guess.
- Get your butt out of there.
- That's a good idea.
- Hey, yeah that's
a good idea.
Heck, I was weaned
on paint thinner,
that's why I didn't think
of that (goofy laughing).
- Hey you guys, how
about a flipping
for little odds,
what do you say?
- Nobody wanna,
forget your odds, man.
(all chattering)
- [Tom] Shadow of death.
And so, the Apostle
Peter awoke with the sun
and verily he heard a voice,
"A cock will cry three times
before you betray Rommel."
- [Joel] And I just
remembered it's like 12 noon,
and they still make them
sleep, this is a really dumb
camp.
(imitating snoring)
- Right foot, left foot,
biggest damn
thing in the case.
- [Tom] Christian squeaks,
firing, fiddling, Rome.
- [Joel] We're rocks and
we're smarter than this cast.
- [Tom] Let's
get out of here.
I'm really tired
of this movie.
- Come on, you guys.
(doors closing)
- Boy, that Rommel
guys is really cool.
I wish we could
be more like him.
- Yeah, well we
can never be him,
all we can do is
try to emulate him
and tell others the
good news about Rommel.
I read his book, you know,
he is a magnificent bastard.
But in it, they
had the patterns on
how to make this
super cool hat.
Check them out, you guys.
- Gimme, gimme, gimme.
- They're really cool, yeah.
- And there's a lot
of neat things here.
- Love is good.
- Anyway, there's a lot
of neat things you can do
as Rommel, like obviously
go sidehacking, you know.
- Or, you can take your
refrigerator around the
world.
- Right, that's a good idea.
Or, you can entertain
guests at your summer home.
- Yeah, and then there's
running through the woods
and rolling down hills
with your best girl, Rita.
(dissonant guitar)
Ah, Rita!
- Aw, man, come on, Crow.
In every life a
little rain must fall.
Let's try to concentrate
on some of the
more positive things
here about Rommel.
- Oh, don't forget
the fun he had
playing with his mechanic
pal, playing pool
to forget about what
happened to his girl, Rita.
(dissonant guitar)
- Aw, you got
to take it easy.
Come on, there's
still a lot of
really neat stuff
that Rommel did.
Like, remember
that time he got
really crazy, and went
into town to raise money
to get those
crazed killers to
go and avenge the death
of his girlfriend, Rita?
(crying)
(dissonant guitar)
- Come on, Joel,
snap out of it.
Joel, quick, think of
something to cheer him up.
Think of a joke.
- Yeah, yeah right.
Uh, hey, Joel?
Number eight.
(laughing)
- Oh, I've been
too tense, man.
Yeah, that's a good one,
that's funny all right.
- Ah, something coming
in on the view screen.
(laughing)
No, that's not a
joke, actually.
- No really, there's a
ship coming into range.
- Oh no, you just can't
tell them the way Crow can.
- No he's right, Joel,
there's a ship
coming into range.
- (laughs) He did it
again, that just kills me.
He's so funny.
- [Joel] Wait a minute,
there is a ship out there
and it's got a
sidehack on it.
Hey, who are you?
- Oh come on, Rommel,
you know who I am,
I'm JC from the planet
Five The Hard Way.
Now look, baby, our
senses have indicated that
you've been watching
the Sidehack movie,
hey, which is cool, man.
You know, we were even
going to bring you cats
back down to
Earth, but then you
had to go and be like Rommel.
- [Tom] Oh no, we don't
want to be like Rommel.
- Then why are you wearing
those stupid hats, baby?
- [Joel] I don't know,
what do you have
against Rommel anyway?
- I tried to
show him the way,
I tried to show
him the light.
I was like a brother to him.
Now Cooch, Cooch tell me,
did I love
Rommel, did I, huh?
- That's Gooch!
- Right, right, Gooch, look,
man, I loved him.
My own flesh I
don't love better!
But I wasn't good
enough for him.
How many times I asked
him to ride with me?
He just said no.
I want you to do
something for me, Cooch.
I want you to do something, I
want you to get Rommel for
me.
Get him, get
him man, get him.
- I will.
- All right, good.
- I will get him.
- Cool, baby.
- Just get him.
- I will get him.
- Would you get,
go, get Rommel, go.
Get Rommel.
- I will.
I will get him.
- Wonder what they wanted.
- I wonder, exactly,
what's going on.
- Man, I hate to say
it, but for being
marooned on a satellite, it's
sure getting busy around
here.
- Yeah.
- That's true.
I know that Rommel guy
has a lot on his mind.
We're just not the types
to be carrying around that
kind of psychological pain
and emotional baggage.
- No.
- Yeah, you're right, let's
go  watch the rest of the
movie.
- There's more movie?
(dissonant guitar)
(crying)
(uptempo instrumental music)
(laughing)
- Gooch, I knew
you'd come, numero.
- [Tom] Number eight maybe,
that was really funny.
- We got him!
You know that old rock
quarry where I was
going to hide, the one
with the tin shack?
You tell Rommel that's
where I'm hiding.
You bring him there
in the morning.
The rest of us
will be waiting.
- What for?
I had a hard time
getting out of there.
- Cooch.
- Coochy, coochy, cooch.
- You're my back.
- [Joel] He's insane,
not everything he says
has to make sense.
- [Tom] Yeah.
(drum rolling)
And we'll be right back
after this message.
- (laughs) We got him, honey.
- [Joel] Eee.
- [JC] I got him.
- [All] Great.
- [Joel] Um, you
kiss like a duck.
Honey, your mere touch
makes me physically ill.
- Don't talk with
your mouth full.
I feel my lunch is coming up.
- I've got to get
away from you.
- [JC] All of a sudden
you've got to get away, hun?
Where do you think
you're going to go?
- I met a nice guy
called Ike Turner.
- [JC] You don't know
what you're talking about.
- I know exactly what
I'm talking about.
- (laughs) You know, you know
you were dying for me to
take you out of
that one horse town.
- [Tom] She's from Chicago.
- You know, sometimes
I think you're crazy.
What would you do
without me, huh?
- I guess she'd heal.
- I don't know, but
at least I wouldn't
have to be doing
anything I didn't feel.
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
- [Joel] Oh, that hurt.
- [Tom] And that was
a romantic don't.
(coughing)
- Maybe you better explain
more about those feelings.
- And be specific,
use specific examples.
- In fact, you seemed
to like the whole scene.
- Are you trying
to tell me you were
playing some kind
of game in bed?
- [Joel] Yeah,
Parcheesi, and I lost
a lot of my game pieces.
- Now I want out.
I don't know who I despise
more, you or myself.
- [Tom] Or the devil
or Chuck Logan.
(yelling)
(slapping)
- Is that a bad topic?
- I suppose you'd
like it with Rommel?
Do your part, huh, huh?
Or maybe it was the
other way around, huh?
- [Joel] They don't have
a healthy relationship.
- [Tom] Not at all.
- I'll show you what.
Or was it the
other way around?
- [Joel] Um, could you
let go of my wind pipe?
I'm supposed to leave.
- Routine 37.
- [Tom] I can't believe
that, Wally Carbo.
That's an illegal hold.
Oh, that's an automatic
three day suspension.
(gasping)
- [Joel] Oh, I'm really
glad it's just a movie,
they're just actors.
- [Tom] The money's
in the, ahh.
- "Cops" is filmed
on location.
- I don't want to
make you do things
you can't feel.
What'd you say that for?
- [Tom] JC is
wanted by the FBI.
He should be considered
armed and stupid.
- Huh, huh?
- [Joel] Did I tell you
about the rabbits, George?
- I don't like it when
you say things like that.
- [Tom] I think they're
communicating a lot better
now.
- You didn't
mean it, did you?
I know you're sorry, baby.
I'm not mad.
- [Tom] I'm just
drawn that way.
- Come on, baby, talk to me.
Talk to me, baby.
- Now that you're dead,
I can tell you about
1,000 wonderful lovers.
- Talk to me!
- Say hello to
the folks, Bubby.
- [Tom] Hello, folks.
I will kill you!
Oh, I guess I did.
♪ Slow, slow ♪
♪ Blah blah, slow slow ♪
♪ Slow slow, blah ♪
- [Joel] Hey, nice sweater.
♪ Slow, slow ♪
♪ Blah ♪
- Huh, he really is bad.
- [Tom] He's biting his
nails,  that's really
disgusting.
♪ Slow, slow ♪
- You're no better than JC
if you go through with this.
- Luke, I'm going to
tell you something.
It's easy for you to
come out here preaching
to me about what I
should or shouldn't do.
- [Joel] And what
you shouldn't wear.
- There's only one
difference, it wasn't Lois.
- Ah, Tony Tinell
wants her hat back.
- Maybe you're
right, I don't know,
but give yourself some
time and think it out.
- [Tom] McCloud!
- There's only one
thing I can think about.
- [Joel] Uh, my next line.
- Jc.
- [Crapa] Hey, Rommel?
- [Tom] You
magnificent son of a--
- Gooch is back.
- [Joel] And there's
gonna be trouble.
- [Tom] Hey la lee la.
- Is it still dark?
- [Joel] Yeah.
I'm Cooch and
I'm gonna go hide
in a little wrap, and then
I'm gonna cover myself up,
and leave my little
butt hanging out, yeah.
- Well, let's go kill him.
- Good morning, dummy.
Wake up and die.
- [Tom] (imitates
snoring) Oh, hi.
- [Man] You trust him?
- [Joel] What?
- What?
- [Tom] What did I do?
- [Joel] What, I
didn't do anything.
What's the deal, I
didn't do nothing?
- I go to the bush and you
guys make a big deal out of
it.
- [Joel] He went to
the bush for two hours.
- We've been sitting here
over an hour waiting for you.
You moonlighting on us, boy?
- Reading a magazine.
- [Joel] Geez, you know.
- I say he's a spy.
- [Joel] I think
he's a sailor.
- Is that true, boy?
Huh, you settin' us up?
- Come on, man,
it's a bad joke.
- (chuckles) You
know, number 12.
- Hey, what are you
guys trying to do?
- [Joel] Wear this hat.
- [Jake] Here, I'll find out.
- [Joel] This ought
to jog his memory.
- You got something to say?
(yelling)
- Put me down you
son of a bitch!
- Uh, no, that's
the wrong answer
but thanks for playing.
- [Man] Easy, Cooch.
- [Tom] It's Gooch.
- Here, grandpa, catch.
- You guys are cra--
(groans)
- [Man] True boy, true.
- Son of a--
- You magnificent son of a,
(groans)
- You going to tell
me where he is?
- There's nothing to
tell, I went to the brush.
- Now listen, I'm going
to ask you one more time.
Where is he?
- I don't know where he is.
He's up at the town, I swear.
- [Tom] I've got
nowhere else to go!
(groaning)
- [Joel] I'm a lot
smarter now, thanks.
- Rock quarry, rock quarry.
He told me to bring you
there in the morning.
- [Joel] You got a
little on your nose.
- Now, what's he going
to do after we get there?
- [Joel] Uh, have
a late breakfast.
- [Gooch] All he told me was
to bring you there, that's
all.
- Did he say anything
about what time?
I like to be prompt.
- Grab him, tie him up.
- [Joel] And don't be
afraid to use a granny knot.
- I'm sure glad you've
come back old buddy.
- [Man] I never
met a spy before.
- [Man] Just tie him
up and make it snappy.
- Luke, I'd like you
to do me a favor.
- [Tom] We really are
good friends, aren't we?
- What?
- [Joel] Stand
a little closer.
- I want to bring
the police out here.
- You mean, I've finally
gotten through to you.
- Yep, you finally
got through to me.
- Well, it's about time,
let's get the hell outta
here.
- Now I know where he's at,
I'm not letting him get away.
- Okay, okay, but don't
you start nothing.
I'll be back in
an hour or so.
- Okay, I won't start
nothing, I promise.
We'll meet you at the
rock quarry, okay?
- Okay.
(uptempo instrumental music)
- [Joel] And then
things got really weird.
Acid Canyon.
(mysterious
instrumental music)
- Now, this is how
you do a monkey.
And you crouch a little
lower to do an orangutan.
- [Joel] Just as I suspected.
This is where they shot
the "Love Shack" video.
- [Tom] Oh.
Pitiful.
(imitates percussion)
You got a little on the--
♪ I got a bike that's
as big as a whale ♪
Get him with
the 10 foot pole,
that'll work
really well, yeah.
- Hmm, moose track.
Two, three day old.
- [Joel] You think
you've got problems,
I'm not even supposed
to be in this film.
- [Tom] Gary Collins, today
at four on Hour Magazine.
- [Joel] Hey, it's
Cheech Marin, huh.
- Poison still fresh.
- [Joel] I'm a little rabbit,
sneaky, sneaky, sneaky.
- It's the cap snaffler.
- [Tom] It really,
really works.
Oh, don't grab his
gun, no guns, uh uh.
No bongos.
- [Joel] Is it hot out
here or is it just me?
- [Tom] No sweaters.
- Not allowed.
- [Tom] I'll just walk under
the cover of this air here.
- [Joel] I set my own
trap, then I go after him.
(yelling)
Have a little
fire, scarecrow.
(gun firing)
- [Tom] Shot with
a tomato gun.
- [Joel] Ooh.
- [Tom] No drumming,
not allowed.
- [Joel] Hey, they're
playing In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida.
How annoying.
- Jc!
Jc!
- Whee.
- [Man] JC, JC!
- Soylent Green is
made from people!
- [Man] Don't shoot, JC!
(guns firing)
- [Joel] Yeah, I'm
quick on the draw.
Nice, huh?
Yikes.
(whistling)
- You know, boy, I never did
think this thing would work.
- Ouch.
- Come on now, let's
go, let's move it.
- [Joel] Yeehaw.
- Hey, they're
riding number 15.
That reminds me of a
joke, number 16 (chuckle).
(suspenseful
instrumental music)
(guns firing)
- [Joel] I kind of wish
that was the director there.
- [Tom] Yeah.
Hm, okay, I just
changed my policy.
Everybody use guns.
(laughing)
- Number 16.
(guns firing)
- [Joel] If the bullets don't
kill them, the music will.
- [Tom] Yeah.
(gun firing)
- [Joel] Uh,
more dead people.
Funny, huh?
- [Tom] Yeah.
(guns firing)
- [Joel] Got him again.
- [Tom] Amazing.
- Came out of tuck too early.
- [Tom] I know, too bad about
having to die like that.
Ah, our contractual
obligation
to this movie is over.
- No guns?
What the heck was I thinking?
- [Joel] Yeah, I'll just hide
behind these blades
of grass here.
That's going to help.
- [Tom] Okay, okay I've got
to remember that I'm crazy.
Note to myself, load guns
before killing spree.
Yeah.
Okay, yep.
(suspenseful
instrumental music)
- That's right,
pretend you're hurt.
- [Tom] Ouch.
- Honey lips?
- What are we gonna
do now, lover?
- [Joel] Oh, what's
that supposed to mean,
you're coming on to me?
- It's the end of the line!
I never met a general before!
Why don't you come on over,
we can get acquainted!
(chuckles)
- [Joel] Yeah.
- You're not talking.
- [Tom] And that hurts
me, we never talk anymore,
you're so distant.
Where's the love?
- Have nothing to say?
- I'm sorry!
Wait, what am I
apologizing for?
- [Joel] Well, this isn't
gonna take a licking,
keep on ticking.
Only you understand me.
- All right, all right!
- You said that.
- [JC] I'm coming out!
- [Tom] I'm coming
out and I don't have
any jewelry or accessories.
- [Joel] I am Keyrock.
- Just you and me!
- [Tom] And a dog named Boo!
- Join me and all
this can be yours.
- [Joel] So, it's
been a while.
Good to see you
again and all.
- [Tom] Yeah, hey,
what's been going on
ever since you
and I said, huh!
- Oh, why didn't I
get out of his way?
(laughing)
(grunting)
- [Tom] Routine 37,
I should have known.
- Oh.
There he goes.
- [Joel] Oh, there's a
foreign object in that ring.
- [Tom] Uh-oh.
- Meanwhile,
12,000 miles away,
Acrin's best speed toward the
hills of Southern California.
Oh, Andy, faster.
(grunting)
- [Tom] Ow, that's
my sore arm.
Ow, that's not fair.
- Whoa.
- [Joel] Aw, it hurts inside.
- Ayekeeba!
- [Joel] That'll teach
you to fall under
a conveniently placed cable.
(chocking)
- So you think I need
bridge work, huh?
Oh, okay.
(gasping for air)
- [Joel] I love you.
- [Tom] Are you
gonna sit down
and work this
thing out or what?
- Oh, what a karate chop to
the head, the neck, the body.
(mumbling)
(grunting)
A lot of grunting going on.
- [Joel] I always
did love you.
And he missed.
- They're in a rut.
(grunting)
I'm sorry, what did you say?
- [Joel] Yeah, come, come
over to this other rut.
That's better, isn't it?
- Oh, you took my thumb.
Charlie, you took
my thumb, Charlie.
- [Joel] Aw, Charlie.
Meanwhile on the
plains of Nebraska,
the car speeds forward.
(grunting)
- [Tom] That had to sting.
Oh, that one really hurt.
You crushed it, you crushed
it, it hurts and stuff.
- [Joel] Throw him to
the ground, centurion.
You're lucky my chick's
not here, you know that?
(siren wailing)
- Well okay, you bum.
But if you do it again,
you get more of the same.
- [Tom] We didn't figure
this into the formula.
(gun firing)
- Oh.
- [Joel] Okay, Paul.
- [Joel] Oh, brother.
- What?
- [Joel] I hope this
doesn't happen when you die.
That would really
be upsetting.
- [Tom] This was all
supposed to be a dream here.
How does that go down?
- So, I guess there's
not going to be
anymore sidehacking, huh?
- [Tom] I don't think so.
- [Joel] Siedhacking
on a coffin, maybe.
- Side coffin.
- [Joel] Is that possible?
- [Tom] It's possible.
Oh, that's clever.
- [Joel] Didn't
the Munster's car
used to have a side coffin?
- No, no, grandpa
drove a coffin.
- [Joel] Yeah, that
was the dragster one
and there was the
big town car one.
- Yeah.
Are you trying to
change the subject?
- [Joel] No, no.
- [Tom] I'm impressed.
♪ Forever ♪
♪ Only love ♪
♪ That's the fun ♪
- This film was also released
as Million Dollar Legs.
- [Tom] I thought so.
Isn't that Ginger
Rogers there I saw?
- Most of her
scenes were cut.
- [Tom] Oh.
♪ That's the fun ♪
- [Tom] There's those
Tessier sisters again.
- [Joel] Well, we
better get out of here.
Our job is done.
- [Crow] The Tessier goyals.
Ha ha, get it?
(doors slamming)
- Oh brother, that
was so crappy.
- Boy, what a
depressing film.
- Yeah, talk about nihilism,
that's the second
film in a row
that had the hero
die in the end.
- Boy, we're never
going to snap out of
this existential dilemma.
- Oh, I was afraid
this would happen,
so I brought
this thing along.
(light piano music)
- But, Joel, why was
the movie so bad?
- Yeah, it was cool in the
beginning with the
sidehacking,
then it went right down
the drain and they had to
pad out the rest of the
film with all that killing.
- Oh no, Crow, it wasn't
killing that padded out the
film.
- No?
- Only love pads the film.
♪ When sorries were young
and dreams were not done ♪
♪ And sorrow
was so far away ♪
♪ A storybook scene
with songs to be sung ♪
♪ And life, life
was just for today ♪
- Oh, Joel.
♪ But nothing lasts forever ♪
♪ Only love, pads the film ♪
♪ Of all the dreams
you treasure ♪
♪ Only love, love
pads the film ♪
- Joel, may I?
- Please.
♪ Love that you made
with two hearts as one ♪
♪ Are flowers that
blow in the wind ♪
Crow?
♪ You give all you take ♪
♪ A day in the sun ♪
♪ But even the
sun must descend ♪
- Everybody now, come on.
♪ La la ♪
♪ But nothing lasts forever ♪
(crying)
♪ Only love ♪
♪ Pads the film ♪
♪ Of all the dreams you
treasure, treasure ♪
♪ Only love pads the
film, pads the film ♪
- Aw, Gypsy.
♪ Scientists are calling ♪
♪ And now better get going ♪
(crying)
- Listen to them up there.
Singing and dancing their
dear little hearts out.
Oh those poor, I'm going
to bring them down.
- Oh, why don't we invite the
entire King family in here.
- Oh and the cow's
frozen up with people.
- Oh, never mind.
And don't you have some
letters to read, pink boy?
- Yeah, of course, I
got them right here.
Let's see, Cambot, put
that one up on the screen.
Oh, it's just print but
they should see it anyway.
"For Joel, Tom
Servo, and Crow."
- [Crow] Hey.
- [Joel] "I'm 13 years old
"and my family loves
your show a lot.
"Every time we watch it,
"we can't stop laughing."
- [Tom] Aw.
- "The best I like
is the nice tag
"or nice dive, and
the bot sitcom.
"Well you might need a
calculator," he says.
You remember that,
when you said--
- Oh yeah, sure.
- The twins.
- "And when Tom Servo,
Crow, sometimes Gypsy
"play when they have
to tell something good
"and play bad about the
movie for gram chips."
- Oh, he thought they're--
- He thinks they're
called gram chips.
- We all know gram chips.
- "But anyway, that's from
With Laughs from Chris
Tacket."
Maybe we can do a good thing
and a bad thing
about that letter.
You got a good thing to say?
- The good thing is, well--
- Gram chips.
- Well, I'm just so
full of love right now,
I can't say a bad thing
Chris, I love you.
- What about you?
Got a bad thing to
say about that letter?
- Uh, the printing's nice.
- Okay, that's a bad thing?
- Uh, yeah.
- Of course.
If you've seen Joel write--
- Anyway, let's put that.
Cambot, let's put that
address up on the screen,
- and Tom Servo, do the
mighty voiceover, please.
- Okay, send your
letters to the
"Mystery Science Theater
3000" Information Club.
That's post office box
5325 Hopkins Minnesota.
Zip is 55343.
And we love you.
- Okay, and the
next one, Cambot,
put this one up
on still store.
- [Tom] Oh, nice.
- [Joel] This one says,
"Dear Go," which is Joel.
"Surbo and Crow."
- [Crow] Hey.
- [Joel] "I really like SF
and  I don't mean San
Francisco."
- [Tom] (chuckles)
A little joke there.
- "And I like
Tom Surbo best."
It's Tom Servo, by the way.
- I'm glad you're reminding.
- "Because he's cute."
- Aww.
- "I like Crow because
he always makes me laugh.
"I would really like for
another robot to be on the
show,
"but not a boy or a girl.
"I would like
her to look like.
"PS, I drew a picture
on the back but I want
"one girl for Crow."
"Here she is."
- Yeah, me too.
- "One for you, Joel."
But it's kind of just
Gypsy, a redesign of Gypsy.
We've already got
a girl here, silly.
- We love Gypsy.
- Anyway, I guess
that ought to do it.
What do you think, sirs?
- I think I liked it.
Well, until next
time, Joel Ackerson.
Go ahead, Frank,
push the button.
- I will.
- Well push it.
- I will push the button.
- Push the button, Frank.
- Just push the button.
- I will.
- Push.
- Make one of these--
- I will push the button
- And do this.
- [Frank] I will
push the button.
(slow instrumental music)
(whooshing)